[suspenseful music]
NEXT TIME, BE CAREFUL
WHO YOU MESS WITH!
[inaudible dialogue]
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING,
DON'T YOU FORGET THAT.
[inaudible dialogue]
[Rob screaming]
[henchmen laughing]
[humming] ♪ Cosmic... ♪
[giggles]
[in English] We need an extra table.
Ah! You can get the side table
in the bedroom.
[in Filipino] All right.
[Karylle singing] ♪ Cosmic... ♪
[door lock beeps]
[Karylle humming]
[Karylle vocalizes]
- [knocking on door]
- [vocalizing stops]
[tense music]
[exhales sharply]
Oh? You changed the combination?
Mm... Yeah.
So I have no use for this.
You aren't using the couch I sent?
- Uh...
- It's so hot.
It doesn't really match
the rest of my stuff.
- That's from France, you know.
- [exhales sharply]
Mama.
What are you doing here?
You won't answer my calls or texts.
You blocked me on social media.
What's going on?
You know what's going on.
I don't feel like talking about it.
You've been giving me
the cold shoulder for weeks now.
Our fans are starting to wonder.
[Zsa Zsa] I don't want them to think
there's anything wrong between us.
Isn't there?
Let them think what they want.
Don't be ungrateful.
The fans and reporters have been
supporting us all these years!
They're your fans, Mama, not mine.
And I'm okay!
[Karylle] I'm happy with what I have.
You mean to say...
you're happy wasting all your talent?
[Zsa Zsa] And what's all this?
Why not use the studio
that I always use?
Times have changed, Mama.
And I'd rather do things my way.
When will you prioritize your career?
And by "career",
I don't mean those "gigs".
You just don't get it.
I love singing!
And I love hosting!
You're right. I don't get it.
But I want you
to be successful like me.
I just don't measure success
by selling out arenas like you.
And I don't need to be a poor copy
of my "Divine Diva" mother.
[suspenseful music]
[Rina] Shoot.
Andrea...
You should have waited for me.
How long did you plan this?
How deep did you dive into my life
so you could hurt me like this?
Tell me.
[Andrea] No wonder.
No wonder you knew my favorites.
From drinks to food...
You even knew
I freaking loved dimsum!
It's not what it looks like.
Oh, yeah? Tell me what it looks like!
It's not like that...
What?
You knew everything about me.
You were so perfect.
And I never saw this coming.
Cassie chose you.
She picked you over me.
- She picked you.
- Wow.
Okay.
What a soap opera this is!
Nice. What a pitch, tell me more!
[shouts] Fine! Okay!
I was going to lead you on,
and then I was going to drop you.
Why me?
- [Rina] Babe...
- No, don't!
Don't fucking "babe" me.
- Please.
- No!
I didn't know I was...
- You tricked me!
- Believe me, I love you!
- Oh, my god, leave!
- Babe.
- Leave before I hurt you!
- Please, believe me.
Oh, my god, just leave! Leave!
Leave now!
I'm so sorry.
- Leave now.
- I promise I...
Leave now, Rina.
Please!
[sobs]
[glass shatters]
[theme music]
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ The world is full
Of jealous people ♪
♪ When envy strikes,
It means trouble♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
♪ We always need to be careful ♪
♪ Prying eyes ready to snoop ♪
♪ Digging for the juiciest scoop ♪
♪ That's why we need to be careful ♪
♪ Careful, careful ♪
[tense music]
[air conditioner motor whirring]
[lively music]
[inaudible dialogue]
Thank you, Lord, the AC's fixed.
Perfect. Are they here?
Kelly Norman will be late.
They're stuck in traffic.
It'll be 45 minutes.
Really?
I'm not going to make it to see Joey.
Should I see them in your place?
A manager needs to sign the contract.
Oh, my god. So what do we do?
I need a refill.
[Chin sighs]
Of course, he won't make it...
What are you on about?
Hollywood is late.
Sir Gab can't leave.
So he won't make it to see Joey?
Exactly.
I have an idea.
[Chin] Huh?
- Is he in there?
- Mm-hm.
[line ringing]
Hello? We need your help.
[in English]
Chin, what do you call this?
Oh, that one is called bibingka.
- Oh!
- A rice cake with salted egg in it.
- [Kelly] Salted egg?
- [Chin] Yeah!
Could you get those notes for me,
the latest from the director?
[Kelly] Okay. All right, then. Uh...
Gabriel, is there a problem?
No, everything's great.
Great.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm Matthew Buenaventura.
You must be Kelly.
That's correct! Lovely to meet you!
My pleasure!
Kelly, I just need a minute.
I need to talk to Gabriel.
- Okay, yeah, sure.
- Okay.
[in Filipino] Let's go.
[Kelly in English] Okay.
[Chin] Okay!
- Have you tried this one?
- What's going on?
No, I haven't tried that one.
[Matthew in Filipino]
These are Deo's keys.
Take his bike, you can still make it.
- Are you sure?
- Just go. Go.
[Gab] Thank you!
[engine revving]
[thrilling music]
[engine sputters]
[thrilling music stops]
[heroic music]
[heroic music continues]
[inaudible dialogue]
Drop me off over there.
Okay, this is fine right here.
Thank you!
Go ahead.
[Gab] I'm sorry.
Are you sure I can't go in?
[somber music]
[sighs]
Daddy!
Joey?
[Gab] Joey!
- [chuckles]
- [relieved sigh]
Gab, you made it!
The traffic is horrible.
Are you okay?
Long story, but I'm here.
Joey.
Your Auntie Sofie
wants you to have this,
so you won't forget her.
I'm not forgetful.
You are, Daddy.
Right.
I'm the forgetful one.
But...
But I promise, this time
I'll always think about you.
[in English] You're crying!
[chuckles]
[in Filipino]
You know how to take pictures
and videos on your phone, right?
And I taught you how to email,
remember?
So send me stuff every day, okay?
Promise me you'll do that.
[Lora] Gab.
[whispers] We have to go.
[Gab] I love you.
[Joey] I love you too, Daddy.
[somber music]
Go!
Gabriel@shine.com.ph.
[in English]
I will never forget about you.
Canadian English!
[in Filipino] Cool!
Say bye-bye!
Bye!
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello, handsome.
- [Rob over phone] Chin.
[crying in pain]
[Rob] Chin.
[tense music]
[Chin] Excuse me.
[exclaims]
I think that's him over there.
I can't open my eyes, Chin!
Can you try walking?
Come on, carefully.
[grunts]
[groans]
[groaning continues]
I did you a huge favor.
[chuckles] Well, why not?
I'm letting you crash here!
[both laugh]
Seriously, cheers to you, Matty.
Thank you for saving me.
And, uh...
to Camille!
Wow, she's a good kid!
Yeah, she's a good kid.
To Camille!
- To Camille! Cheers!
- [knocking on door]
[Gab] Hey.
The first one fucking left me.
And this other jerk
catfished me first before leaving me!
Why didn't she just stab me
to get it over with quicker?
You said you threw her out.
Whose side are you on?
- I'm clearly the victim here.
- No, I...
Right, right.
[knocking on door]
Oh! That could be Rina.
Smack her one.
[Matthew chuckles]
- Hey, Gab...
- Mm!
Looks like we'll need more...
- [Gab] Oh!
- [Andrea] Oh!
...booze.
He wasn't hit in the head
but he should get a CT-Scan anyway,
Uncle Matthew.
[Rachel] I can schedule that
when I take my shift at the hospital.
Okay.
Thank you, Rachel.
And, uh...
not a word to anyone, please.
Absolutely, Uncle Matt.
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
- [Rob] Thank you.
Try not to move too much.
You have to rest.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Even when they were doing it
I was numb.
- Rob...
- Chin.
Rob, you shouldn't have gone there.
Sandra insisted.
She said just one last time.
Try to remember everything.
Everything.
How can I forget?
Uh...
I mean
for you to tell the cops and lawyers.
What?
No. No way.
What do you mean "no way"?
This is my fault.
[Matthew in English]
Nobody deserves this.
[in Filipino]
No, but it's still my fault.
So I just waited for them to finish.
As long as they didn't kill me.
Slowly...
I couldn't do that to my Mom.
Rob.
Don't be afraid.
He won't get away with this.
We'll protect you.
We'll fight this. Okay?
How?
[Andrea] What? What do you mean?
This is Frank Villacin.
[henchmen laughing]
[tense music]
[Rob distant screaming]
[Rob] I won't win.
[Andrea] Oh, god.
Can I go home now?
[exhales sharply]
[inquisitive music]
[Elisse] You have the luggage?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, then this pile and this one.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Thank you so much!
- Okay...
- [baby toy rattling]
- Andrea, hi!
- [Andrea] Hi!
[Elisse] Thank you! You're here!
[Andrea] What's up?
The nanny had to leave urgently,
said there was an emergency.
[lively music]
I'm really late for the shoot.
I'm so embarrassed.
Camille will go with you, no worries!
No, they're limiting
the people allowed on set.
So you need a ride? Let's go!
No, the PM sent
the service car for me.
Oh, so...
[awkward chuckle]
Let me know if you
need anything, okay?
[Elisse] Thank you!
I didn't mean to. I beg you, please.
I didn't see or hear anything.
- [Sofie] Sis...
- Bang! Bang!
Do you know you're useless right now?
I was so close! I was feeling it!
Come on, I've killed you
so many times today.
You're over-rehearsed.
- You're fine.
- But I have to be perfect.
It's my first movie! Noemi, please!
Hey, Camille, help me. You do it.
So sorry, Sofie, too busy.
Bang, bang...
You do it, Noemi, please. Come on.
Come on. Just one more, I promise.
- Fine, I'll do it.
- [Matthew] Noemi?
[Noemi] Oh! Sir Matthew.
Sorry.
[giggles]
[Noemi] Yes, sir?
Hey, can you help me?
A "bang", that's all. "Bang."
Bang!
Hi, guys, Pauline here!
So for today, we're going to be doing
some unboxing for some workout gear.
A weighted jump rope
that I can play around with.
[Pauline] They also sent
a hip resistance band that's pink.
And I'm so excited to use this
in my next training
and I can't wait to show you guys
the next unboxing. Take care.
That's all? That's it?
Mm-hm. That's it.
[in English]
But that one video will be posted
across all of her
social media accounts.
Well, doesn't seem like much.
Should we even make an effort?
Hm.
Definitely.
[Matthew] That's how much
she's getting?
Nope.
This is what SAM is getting from her.
- All that?
- Uh-huh.
For 15 seconds?
Uh-huh.
Well, not bad!
[in Filipino] Let's make some more.
Mm-hm.
[in English] Wait.
I have one more question.
What is it?
What is "unboxing"?
[chuckles]
[Felize crying]
[Camille] What is Ms. Andrea doing
with a baby?
- [Felize crying]
- [Andrea grunts]
Okay, who knows how to do this?
[Felize wailing]
Camille.
- Camille!
- [Camille] Yes, Ms. Andrea.
Bring this all up to my office!
Yes, ma'am.
Why does it have to be a baby...
[Matthew] It's just one day.
[Gab] I remember
when Joey was this age.
- Andrea...
- Yeah.
[in English] Taking care of a baby
is like taking care of your talents.
- Really?
- [in Filipino] Yeah!
Wait, which talents?
Uh... Maricel.
- [chuckles]
- Monsour-Lav.
[laughs]
What if I do something wrong?
[Gab] Then have a meeting with it.
That's all there is to it, right?
- You can leave now.
- [boys laughing]
- [shouts] Camille!
- [Felize crying]
I need a meeting.
[Felize wailing]
When did you learn how to cook?
- Have you tasted...
- Bang!
Not yet!
- Sorry!
- One more line before that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But you know you can do it.
And Chin will be with you.
No need, I know you're all busy here.
- It's okay!
- No way.
This is your first project
as an actor represented by SAM.
We should document everything.
Okay, one more!
One more? How many does it take?
You're good to go!
[Sofie] But you just said it!
I should always be at my best
and make SAM proud!
So one more!
I'm already proud, but okay.
- Let me see the script.
- Okay.
So I'll know when to come in.
This part! Don't forget.
You forgot this part.
- [Gab] This one?
- [Sofie] And one more.
Hey!
Deo!
[Sofie] Deo, over here.
Can you fix this?
GOSSIP TRIO
- So Brandon Vera...
- The MMA fighter?
Correct! And his wife Jessica
are rumored to be splitting
and a third party is involved!
They've been at odds for a while.
But when we see them in public
they're so sweet and touchy-feely.
That's called overcompensation!
They want to tap out
on their marriage.
Is that really what you want?
Well, no one's stopping you!
[laughs]
It couldn't have come from our side.
It's almost impossible!
Nobody knows our situation,
not even at home.
[over phone]
They never, ever see us fight!
You guys have a lot of employees.
[Brandon] I bet you
one of them leaked this story.
Of course they know.
I work with these people.
How can they help me keep your secret
if they didn't know the full story?
So the leak really came from you!
We won't do that to our own talents.
Let's just ask Ogie Diaz, then!
No! They'll doubt you guys even more.
[Brandon] Hey, you better fix this.
I don't want anybody coming after us
for breach of contract.
Nobody wants that.
Just keep on doing what you're doing.
Please, man.
[Matthew over phone] Okay. Stay safe.
I never told anyone, Sir Matthew.
Everything I know
stays in this office.
I know.
You, I trust.
But who's doing this?
I'll try to find out.
I don't know how, but I'll try.
Not everything should be exposed.
That's why I'm hiding these cables.
[suspenseful music]
[doctor] So far, all is well.
Everything looks okay.
And good for you
you're not keloidal.
Those scabs on your body
will lighten eventually.
- Okay?
- [Rob] Doc...
I feel great!
[doctor] Good, then I guess
you're clear for now!
Perfect. Okay, thanks, Doc!
Thank you.
[mouths] Okay?
[doctor] Nurse Rachel
will see you out.
[Rob] Thanks, Doc!
Hey, how about a picture with Rob?
- [Chin] Rob, is it okay?
- [nurse] Sir, just one picture.
[Chin] Just a picture.
Okay, one, two, three, smile!
Can you take a picture on mine too?
- [Chin] Right away, come on!
- [nurse] Thank you.
Okay. One, two, three, smile!
- Thank you!
- Thank you! Let's go.
- Oh, my god! We want pictures too!
- [Chin] No, sorry...
Sorry, excuse us.
- We have another meeting to go to.
- [woman fan] Just one!
Sorry, we're in a rush.
We waited for nothing.
[nurse] Sir, excuse me, sir!
Excuse me, you left your phone.
- Take care.
- [Chin] Thank you.
How's the Vivamax project going?
My siblings are so excited.
Your siblings?
[chuckles]
Yeah, we need a new laptop.
[Rob] It's an old model.
But we used it a lot.
I'm okay, Chin!
Are you sure?
Are you sure you don't need
any justice for what happened?
I'm done with all of it.
I'm a changed man.
What if, and this is
a huge "what if"...
What if someone else exposes
what Frank Villacin did to you?
Chin! Don't do it.
I'm serious.
I don't want you involved in this.
I said it was a "what if".
Where the hell have you been?
The toilet.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
[Andrea] "Feed every four hours..."
"Don't forget to sterilize..."
Now how do I do that
if the sterilizer isn't here?
Okay.
"Check diaper every 30 minutes."
Check diaper every 30 minutes.
How cute!
Post that and you're fired.
- No, I won't.
- [Andrea] Hey, K.
- Hi!
- Hi, how are you?
What's up?
Sit!
Hey, baby!
We just want to show you
what we've been working on.
- Super exciting!
- Okay.
- It's amazing, Ms. Andrea!
- What's all this?
We posted Karylle's latest songs
on YouTube Music.
We already have so many likes!
She's amazing!
♪ Mix the beat of... ♪
[Andrea] I see you enjoyed
working on this.
It always feels good to make music,
especially if there's no pressure.
This is so much fun!
♪ 'Til everything's
Fine, fine, fine ♪
♪ We crawl and we stop,
We walk and we run ♪
[Camille] The posts
are so well-received.
On all her socials,
the reaction is great!
So I made these for her.
[Andrea] Mm...
Nice! Good job.
Camille, next time, I'd appreciate it
if you let me know beforehand.
Yes, ma'am.
I think Matt and Gab
would like to see that as well.
Um... But you know,
you're serving it!
- You're serving it.
- [squeals]
She's so creative
and so chill to work with!
Uh-huh.
She's so good at what she does.
Should I call them, or you?
No, I will, of course. Here I go.
Gosh. It's so hot today.
It's sunny outside,
but raining in here?
I know, right?
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
What's that noise?
A meeting, as usual.
Karylle is in there.
They're meeting about her socials.
Everyone?
- Mm-hm.
- [Daisy] Uh-huh.
Okay.
Your horns are showing, Satan.
What did I say?
What's that?
Set cards.
[Daisy] The meeting's over?
- Yes, it just ended.
- Yes.
What's the fuss
with Karylle's social media?
Glad they liked it,
but Matthew is so funny!
He liked and commented
on my page so much
that he earned a top fan badge!
[Camille] That's why he was asking
about the award he got!
- [Karylle] That's what it was!
- Bye-bye!
Bye, take care! Chin!
How's Rob?
Doing much better, why?
We missed you at the meeting.
We presented artwork
for Karylle's page.
The bosses were so happy!
Oh, well.
You can still help us!
Maybe you can think of more content.
You're so good at stuff like that.
No worries.
Your dad is in the meeting, right?
I'm sure he helped you a lot!
[Sofie] Chin.
Camille.
I'll give you access to the apps.
You are so mean.
[indistinct chatter]
Camille.
[in English] Everybody knows now.
[in Filipino]
It would've been okay if they didn't.
Maybe you shouldn't have told them.
Are Noemi and Chin
giving you a hard time?
Maybe they see me differently now.
[in English]
Like, I don't know if they trust me.
[in Filipino]
This is RM level office politics.
[in English] Well, I trust you.
Matt?
[Matthew] Ricky!
- Is that you?
- Yeah, hi!
[Ricky] Looking good, man!
[Matthew] You too!
Ricky, I'd like you to meet...
I'd like you to meet
my daughter, Camille.
[Ricky] Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, man, my table's over here.
- Okay, see you...
- Good to see you.
[somber music]
[baby toy rattling]
[cell phone ringing]
Elisse? Hi! What's up?
Yeah, actually,
I got Felize's stuff ready.
Yup, I gave her a bath too.
[Andrea] Oh,
and how long is the lock-in?
And why?
Okay, just...
[exhales sharply]
Just keep me posted, okay?
You take care.
Yeah, don't worry. I got you.
Looks like we're having a sleepover.
Is that okay?
[cell phone ringing]
Sofie?
Uh...
Sir Gab, were you asleep?
Uh, no, what's up?
Uh, I called because
I'm really nervous about tomorrow.
I can't sleep.
I'd rather you were nervous
than complacent.
At least now I know
you're taking this seriously.
What if I mess up?
Take two.
What if I get up to take ten?
[chuckles]
If you were the type to do that,
you wouldn't have gotten the part.
[Sofie] But I hear the director
is a diva.
Come on. That's okay.
Besides, Chin will be there with you.
Okay. Thank you so much, Sir Gab.
Sorry I bothered you.
- Thank you.
- Sofie.
You did not bother me at all.
But you should get some sleep.
It's an early call tomorrow.
- Good night, Sir Gab. Thanks again.
- [Gab] Okay? Good night.
I'm sorry.
[sighs]
[line ringing]
Hello, Chin?
I have an idea.
What? Are we doing this or not?
Get a move on! Where is my set up?
The sun is way ahead of us, look!
Enough with the fucking coffee!
THE SOMES SIGNATURE
[rock music]
Oh, now you're running?
Hurry up!
What now?
I'm Lao.
I think we're in this scene together.
Are you alone?
Oh, no, I have...
I have my RM with me.
Do your job, man!
You're messing this up!
It's like dealing with kids!
Animals! You're all stupid animals!
Nobody's moving.
Move!
I think we'll hear "pack up" soon.
Oh, no, really?
I hope not!
No more fucking questions!
Just move the darn thing!
MJ Lastimosa didn't make her flight.
That's the second time she missed it!
What's the problem?
[Richard] Did you follow up on it?
- [AD] Yes, I did.
- [Richard] Huh?
You keep saying yes, darn you
but the call sheet
is a freaking mess.
You're a son of a gun!
You can't fool me
with those puppy dog eyes.
Are you a freaking AD or not?
Yes, I'm an AD.
Then why is this set all messed up?
Send everyone in that scene home!
Now, before I trash
the freaking tent!
- Yes, sir.
- Quickly!
- Faster!
- [AD] We're dropping a scene.
You, you, and you. Pack up, go home.
Don't worry, you're getting paid.
Jay.
Take them to the field cashier.
Now!
[actor 1] Thank you, sir!
[AD] Lao, pack up, you can go.
We'll send for you again soon.
Okay, I'm counting on it.
Thank you!
You're going home?
I have a few more scenes
in this one, anyway.
And I can hop over to another set.
Maybe there's something for me there.
Okay!
I'll ask Mother Aleta
for your number.
Take care.
Uh, sir! What about me?
I'm in the scene with Lao.
But you sent him home.
- Am I done?
- We dropped the scene.
But I still need you, so stay. Okay?
Okay, sir! Thank you!
[camera shutter clicks]
[AD] Tight shot. Close up.
Real close.
Now step back. Take one from here.
Okay.
There, that side.
Sofie, almost done, just a few more.
- Good.
- [Richard] Wait!
What the heck! That blood is lousy!
It's so fake!
This is how it's done!
Now more! More! A lot more!
There! See that?
Now take it again!
Need more blood! Wait!
Not enough blood for me!
Some more. Now take the shot!
Take it!
[AD] I told you to add more.
Wait. More here, more more.
Now, take it! Now that's blood!
Now here, add more and more.
[Richard] Next set up, right away!
We're too slow. Double time!
- Sir!
- Hey, Gab!
- Good afternoon.
- Nice to see you!
- You too!
- Thanks for coming.
- Sure.
- You have an actor here?
Yes, there is!
Are you done with this scene?
- Can you check?
- [AD] Let's see.
We dropped that scene...
- [Gab] Ah!
- ...but we took our photos.
I see. Where's Sofie now?
She's around here somewhere.
Okay! Director Richard,
sorry I bothered you.
I'll just look for my talent.
- Okay, Gab.
- All right.
What are you waiting for?
- Set it up, faster!
- [AD] Jay, get the dolly!
- Oh! Sir Gab!
- [Gab] Surprise!
What are you doing here?
- [Sofie] Can't hug!
- No.
Uh, I called Chin
and told him I would come.
You're done for the day?
Yes, I am.
By the way
I've been calling Chin, but I can't
reach him because of the signal.
Have you spoken to him?
Looks like your visit was a waste.
Not at all!
I try to visit the set
to make sure my artists are safe.
Uh...
[giggles]
Sir Gab, those guys are harmless!
That doesn't happen in real life.
[gasps]
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it that way.
No, it's okay.
Uh...
I'm a bit paranoid lately
because of what happened to Rob.
Um...
Anyway, back to you.
Don't worry,
dropped scenes happen all the time.
I know.
But it's their loss.
They didn't get to see how good I am.
Darn straight!
But we see it all the time.
But it wasn't easy! I was over there!
It's tough playing dead!
- There?
- It was something else.
Yes, right there!
I bet you nailed it!
Of course!
Anyway, Sir Gab,
I'm going back to the office.
Okay!
Let's go back together.
Um...
You know...
You really have an in with me.
I only visit sets
for talents who are special to me.
[giggles]
- Don't get that on me!
- Sorry!
[giggles]
Thanks, bro!
He's our prosthetics guy.
He did my gunshot here.
I can help you with that.
JULIUS AND TINTIN
FOR THE FILIPINO FAMILY
So what's the latest news?
It's a bit sad, the rumors
about an alleged conflict
between mother and daughter
Zsa Zsa Padilla and Karylle.
Oh, Zsa Zsa and Karylle.
It's said that there's a disagreement
on the direction of Karylle's career.
But of course I understand Zsa Zsa.
We want to see our kids,
or in Zsa Zsa's case
her daughter, succeed
or exceed what she has done.
But does a child
really need to follow
in the footsteps
of their famous mother?
Let's wait and see what happens next.
JULIUS AND TINTIN
FOR THE FILIPINO FAMILY
[Daisy gasps] Oh!
What's all this?
Noemi, are we
Rain Artist Management now?
What's going on here?
No idea, and there's more of it now.
This is Deo's fault.
Tomorrow, I should sell
arroz caldo and champorado.
Because it's rainy season in here!
You're not helping, Ms. Daisy.
This is embarrassing! We have guests!
We're soaking our guests!
Oh, we have guests...
[Noemi] So sorry!
[gasps]
Thank you.
Where's Zsa Zsa? I thought... [gasps]
Nothing gets past me.
Just checking for leaks.
No leaks here.
You can shut up now, Deo.
Let's get out of here.
Ms. Andrea has a meeting!
[Noemi] Oh! She's here.
Yours?
Oh! No, no.
Do you know Elisse Joson?
This is her baby.
Of course.
This is Felize
I'm looking after her
while Elisse is at a shoot.
I'm so sorry we have
to keep our voices down.
This one is pretty hard
to put to sleep.
I won't take long.
I just wanted to let you know that
I've been listening
to Karylle's new songs
and I saw her social media page.
♪ Some days we're serious ♪
♪ Some days we laugh like this ♪
- ♪ Some days mysterious ♪
- [Andrea] Isn't it great?
All the RMs
are working on it right now
to get her more followers.
The songs are getting a lot of likes.
And you know what's nice?
We're also getting lots
of hosting gigs for her.
I saw that, and... good job.
- Oh!
- I wanted to let you know
that I'm very grateful
that you're giving Karylle
the extra effort
and attention her career needs.
Oh, that's not difficult to do.
Karylle is so talented!
But somehow,
I can't help but feel that...
I'm holding her back.
She's shutting me out.
And...
That's why
I've decided to leave SAM.
Wait, what? Why?
[in Filipino] I don't want
your attention divided between us.
There's no such thing here,
Zsa Zsa, you know that.
[in English]
I mean, we have lots of artists
but we managers do our best
to take care of each of you.
You know that.
What are you talking about?
I don't want her to blame me
if something doesn't work out.
She thinks of me as a shadow
that she wants to escape.
- She's your daughter.
- Exactly.
I've already made up my mind.
Andrea, please promise me
that you'll give her
everything that you gave me.
- But...
- Andrea, I have to go.
Zsa Zsa, please.
- Can we talk about this first?
- [Felize cries]
Zsa Zsa!
[Felize wails]
Your timing, young lady,
is absolutely impeccable.
[exhales]
- [Chin] Ms. Andrea.
- [Andrea] Hi.
[Chin] What happened?
[Andrea] It's Zsa Zsa.
Never mind.
What's the update on Juan Makabayan?
Um, last I heard, they were using
Bangkok for Spain.
That's old news.
Anything else?
They aren't using Bangkok either.
They might just shoot in Manila.
That's why I can't make
the schedule work.
None of our talents are available
for the new Juan Makabayan timetable.
We may be unable to do this project.
Anyway, where's Camille? Is she here?
What do you need, Ms. Andrea?
I can do it. It's Camille's turn
on the set of Portrait.
[Andrea] Her turn?
Why are you taking turns?
That's Maricel and Snooky together!
If they kill each other today,
Camille can't handle that on her own!
I was supposed to go to Sofie's shoot
but Sir Gab said he'd go.
So what are you still doing here?
You should be at the shoot now
helping Camille out!
If Maricel and Snooky leave us too,
then we're really screwed!
Ms. Zsa Zsa is leaving SAM?
[scoffs]
Ignore me.
Just tell Camille to see me
as soon as she gets back.
[Chin] Will do.
What is up with this office?
[tense music]
[water pattering]
- [Matthew] Yes?
- Sir Matthew?
Just checking if you need anything.
Well, no, nothing urgent.
But if you have time, Noemi
read these, will you?
There might be something good there
for our talents.
Okay.
Oh, by the way
Zsa Zsa is leaving SAM.
Really? Why?
She was talking to Andrea earlier.
Just a heads up.
I'm sure Ms. Andrea
will let you know.
I'm sure.
I'll go.
[Paul] What you have in your hand
is your signing bonus.
What the heck? Hang on a second.
You said that three times already.
Why don't you change it up?
I'm just following the script, okay?
[Snooky] I'm just following
the director.
[Maricel] What are you on about?
You're not the only actor here.
- I am too!
- [Snooky] Oh, come on!
Cut!
[Maricel] Did we get it wrong?
- No, it's all correct!
- All correct!
Yeah, but I want to stop.
Stop? Why?
We've been rehearsing this bit
and rehearsing some more.
Then our co-star comes in
and changes the dialogue anyway!
- [Chin] How are they?
- They've been at it all day.
- Huh?
Screaming at each other
back and forth.
- I need you to clear all this out.
- I think it's Sir Roderick.
[Roderick] I don't want these
distractions disrupting my acting!
Oh, speak of the devil.
Guys, come on! Take a look!
- This is just a suggestion.
- [Mac] Okay...
Wouldn't it be a better angle
- if the camera is there?
- [Mac] Where?
Here, up high over there!
That way, when I come in...
[playful music]
PETRA THE HORSE
AND THE NAUGHTY KITTEN
JACK AND POY
GORIO AND TEKLA
ME AND LITTLE NINJA
SMALL AND TERRIBLE
You know what he said?
He calls our acting old-fashioned.
You're not offended, are you?
Not at all!
- For our film.
- I'll take note.
- He directs his actors?
- The nerve.
You can't fool us, Mr. Javier!
And you can no longer deceive us
with your lies!
We will never believe you!
Beautiful!
That's it?
[Roderick] That's all there is?
I'm sorry, sir, this is all wrong.
I mean...
Where's my script?
No, I have my own script.
I want my script!
My script!
[assistant] Here it is, sir!
Sir, I'm not interfering here.
This is just a suggestion.
- Hang on.
- You're not intruding!
I know, I know!
So we're in the Spanish era, right?
Why don't we do everything
in Spanish, then?
Something like this. Listen.
[in Spanish] "No estoy engañando.
Oh, por favor, creeme!
Este el unico lugar donde
de tratado de sel bueno.
Si sonries, no mi crees, oh!
Melo meresco todo bien
se que soy malo
se que soy malvado!"
Something like that.
- You wrote that?
- Yes.
- [Roderick] Don't be sensitive.
- [Mac] I'm not!
- [Roderick] Don't be mad.
- [Mac] I'm very open.
I'm so open to all this!
- I want to nail this scene!
- We're all very open.
What's that?
You're lighting the scene like this?
Perfect, huh?
Sir, it's too bright!
Bright?
This is a Spanish-era dungeon,
what's all this light doing in here?
Where's the DOP?
Director of Photography?
- Where's the DO...
- Sir?
Hey, young lady, where's the DOP?
- She is the DOP!
- I'm the DOP.
Are you? Sorry!
See that light over there?
It's too bright.
It's like there's a moon in here.
How about you kill it?
Joven, kill this one.
- [Roderick] There!
- [Mac] Better!
- Now it's perfect?
- Yeah, hang on.
Sir, another suggestion.
It's still a bit too bright.
How about we kill this one too?
- Kill it.
- [Mac] Kill it.
Kill it.
- Yes!
- Okay...
- One more, sir...
- One more?
This one is still too bright.
For balance, kill this one too.
Kill it.
- [Roderick] That's it!
- [Mac] Okay... Happy now?
- Happy.
- [Roderick] Hey, my eyes!
What is that?
- A spotlight.
- Sir.
- Top light.
- Hear me out.
Is that fluorescent lighting?
Fluorescent lights didn't exist then.
- Turn it off!
- Turn it off, now.
Get rid of this one too.
- [Roderick] There!
- [Mac] That's it!
[Roderick] Perfecto!
[Mac] You're the best!
You're the Dick!
Let's do a take! Thank you, Dick!
Utility! Coffee! Boiling hot!
[Roderick] Sir,
these are just suggestions...
Small suggestions!
He's so full of himself
like he's everything!
Well, wow!
Just like you!
Me? How am I like him?
Poor you.
Having to deal with this drama.
This is too much for anyone.
You should go back to the office.
Ms. Andrea is looking for you anyway.
- Thank you.
- I'll take care of things here.
Miss Maricel? Miss Snooky? I'm going.
You're leaving?
I might as well leave. Let's go.
#JUSTSHARINGSIS
Hello to my subscribers!
Do you remember the tea last time
about that problematic project
of indie director Lav Diaz
and veteran action star
Monsour del Rosario.
Reports say that their film
can't reach the finish line.
People are stressed.
Some shooting days got wasted.
A lot of back and forth conflicts.
The two can't agree on their vision.
Creative differences, so to speak.
Rumor has it that they're both ready
to just shelve the whole thing
and forget anything happened.
What a shame, right?
#JUSTSHARINGSIS
[Gab] Hey,
are these leaks increasing?
- Hey.
- [Sofie] What's happening?
What a mess!
- [Gab] There are way more leaks now!
- Oh, no.
It's even worse in the rooms.
We brought snacks. Where's Andrea?
Maybe by the swing.
Sofie, can we switch now?
- I have work to do.
- Of course!
- Thank you, Sir Gab!
- Okay!
[Noemi] Oh, Sir Gab, wait!
Why?
Be careful.
Careful? Why?
Zsa Zsa is leaving us.
Ah.
Thank you.
[Noemi] Is that sans rival?
Come on, let's eat!
Yeah, but I'm on a diet.
- Really now?
- But thank you!
Hey, don't I get a bite?
Sir Gab said this was all mine!
You know, you're too much!
He kept you company the whole day
and now you want his food too?
I hope you get diarrhea.
[Gab] What a cute baby!
Give me a kiss.
[Andrea] Hey, quit that!
You're gonna give her rashes!
Baby, monster. What a meanie!
Facial hair is dirty, okay?
Oh, come on.
What are you doing here?
She doesn't like the swing,
so I'm playing with her.
I hear Zsa Zsa is leaving?
[Andrea] How did you know?
[clicks tongue]
Oh, dear.
Aside from that thing with Zsa Zsa
if we don't find out
who's leaking our office secrets.
Brandon and Jessica might leave too!
Plus this Monsour movie,
with no end in sight.
With all the stunts Lav made him do.
It's never-ending.
There's no end to this chaos.
At least Rob is all better now.
But we can't even protect the kid
against Frank Villacin.
And SAM...
We may never be able to buy it!
You can't get a decent answer
out of Matthew.
It's all, "I'll take care of it."
You know how this will end?
We lose not just the artists,
but the entire agency.
[sighs]
Anyway, Elisse called.
She's taking the baby home.
Well...
that's good news, right?
You know, Rina and I talked once.
About adopting a baby.
She always wanted a baby.
Me, not so much.
But now you do?
Well...
People change, you know.
Then have a baby.
I don't think I can have babies
with the people I'm dating now.
I mean, they're not Rina.
You don't need Rina
or anybody to have a baby.
Just do it!
[Gab] There are many ways
to have a baby.
No need to borrow someone else's.
- [babbles]
- [cell phone ringing]
Mommy's calling!
Hi, Elisse!
How are you? Are you done shooting?
Don't worry about Felize.
She's still with me.
And if you need me to still babysit,
I can do it!
- Are you okay?
- [Elisse] Oh, no.
Actually, I'm at your door. I'm here.
- Yes, yes!
- [Andrea] Okay.
- [Elisse] Andrea.
- You wrapped early today!
Great, isn't it? Thank you so much!
- Hi, baby!
- [Andrea] Come in!
[Elisse] Oh, here's her stuff.
So sorry, I'm in a rush.
Oh, no worries.
Um... When is your next shoot?
Um...
- I don't know yet.
- Joseph?
- Can someone help me?
- Of course!
Joseph, help Elisse with her things.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you!
Um...
If you have another shoot,
I'll be here, you know that.
Thank you so much.
But it's all good.
Felize's nanny is back home with me.
- Oh, okay.
- Hey, baby.
- Okay.
- Mommy's here!
Thank you, I owe you one!
- No worries.
- Say bye-bye!
- Bye-bye!
- Bye!
Thank you!
Let's go!
Hey, Elisse?
[dramatic music]
The bruises on his face are healing
after the beating that Rob Gomez got.
Good thing he's recovering quickly.
Or else,
I'd be better-looking than him.
According to my source
Rob's body took a heavy beating
including his business down there.
Scary! The question is
who would do such a thing to Rob?
I know, and I'm sure you do too.
I'll leave it up to you to decide
who this vindictive figure is.
And of course
what did Rob do to deserve this?
Is a woman involved?
[Mr. Fu] I have the answers.
But do I want to share them?
Keep buzzin'!
[Matthew] That's a lot of pictures.
There were some fans
who took pictures with him
at the hospital.
I mean, he still looked great,
despite the bruises.
Chin, you should've stopped them.
I did my best, Ms. Andrea.
I mean, I got him out
of there safely.
The marks on his face are visible.
Yes, we know that.
The pictures aren't the problem.
We all go to the hospital, right?
But the details about his beating?
Matty?
Could it have been your niece?
- [Matthew] Rachel?
- [Andrea] Yeah?
No, not possible.
She's always been very discreet.
Besides, she doesn't even know Rob.
She doesn't care for show business.
[Chin] And when Rob left
the examination room
she stayed behind.
She couldn't have taken the pictures.
So where are those from?
Poor Rob.
[Deo] If I'm being completely honest,
ma'am, sirs...
Uh...
I don't know any of your actors here.
I'm not interested in them.
I only know two.
My idol Monsour
and Brandon, only if he wins fights.
I don't even remember
his wife's name.
So I really don't know this...
Rod Golez?
Rob Gomez.
While we were talking here,
you were by the door.
Were you eavesdropping?
- No.
- Then why were you there?
I was waiting for you to finish.
I left the vacuum cleaner in here.
Well, okay then.
Take it.
[Andrea] Daisy,
we're not done with you.
- Sit down.
- Oh, no.
Ma'am, I swear I didn't do this.
I know nothing.
But you know Cristy Fermin?
Of course I do.
But we're not close.
I don't know her in person.
You didn't message her?
Oh, no, Sir Gab.
I know absolutely nothing about this.
I would never do that to Rob.
[Daisy] He is so kind to me.
And I don't care for tea like that.
It's too scary!
I only remember one rumor I spread.
About Sir Samuel's cause of death.
Now if you don't believe me,
then I'm going to resign.
Daisy, you can't resign.
But you don't trust me anymore!
You can't resign
because you don't work here.
Ms. Andrea, Sir Matt, Sir Gab.
I really know nothing about this.
It wasn't me.
I don't know why, but I believe you.
Don't be mad at us.
We just really need to do this.
You can go, Daisy, thank you.
Thank you!
[Daisy gasps]
Excuse me.
It's not them.
Agree.
But you know what this means, right?
It could be any one of us.
[somber music]
Favorite quote?
"This too shall pass."
The popular
are never popular for life.
The nobodies
won't always be nobodies.
"This too shall pass."
That's what I always tell myself
to keep me on my toes.
To keep me alert.
WHAT'S THE TEA?
WITH OGIE DIAZ
The biggest talent agency here
is Shine Artist Management.
But talk is, it's about to close!
According to rumors
the company will have
new management soon.
Someone wants to take over.
This person is Very Famous.
And get this.
Another one, an Affluent Producer
also wants the company.
[Ogie] But all this talk
about business...
What? It's not me!
Nothing!
Here's what I'm worried about...
[line ringing]
Andrea?
[Andrea] Why is this in the news?
I said it was too early to announce!
Do you think they meant us
when they said "new management"?
Helen hasn't even accepted our offer.
[Matthew] And where do I get
the money to pay for that?
Go back to Gina.
Andrea...
I tried that before.
She doesn't even want to see me.
What if you get a loan from Brandon?
[Matthew] Are you crazy?
That's too risky.
We'll lose any leverage
we still have.
If this goes south one day
and we can't pay him back
he could end up owning SAM.
Okay, scratch Brandon.
Banks. What about banks?
Maybe.
I mean, we're viable.
Maybe with a solid business plan...
Wait.
Closing shop or new management.
[Andrea] What if those two
are the same thing?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
How does that work?
[Andrea] Affluent Producer.
Or AP.
Amir Paul!
What if...
Paul Amir is the new management
who will close SAM down?
Hm?
I'm thinking of something far worse.
[Matthew] Very Famous.
SAM'S NEW OWNER?
VF.
[Gab] VF.
V...
Shoot.
- Frank Villacin!
- [Andrea] Frank Villacin!
SAM'S NEW OWNER?
FRANK VILLACIN
Shoot.
Here's what I'm worried about.
Are their talents aware
of these rumored movements?
It's going to be chaos.
[Ogie] Do they know what's happening?
Does it matter to regular fans?
Not really.
Let's see what happens.
Hold on, let me call somebody.
[ominous music]
To get the latest updates.
[Ogie laughs]
[loud crash]
[water trickling]
[closing theme music]